<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Code03</string>
    <string name="article_title">Article title</string>
    <string name="article_subheading">Article Subheading</string>
    <string name="artical_text">HE U.S. DEATH TOLL from the coronavirus surpassed 20,000 on Saturday as Wyoming became the 50th state to gain approval for a disaster declaration,
        marking the first time in history that every state is under such a declaration simultaneously.
        Wyoming secured consent from President Donald Trump for a disaster declaration, with state health officials reporting just over 260 confirmed cases and no deaths from the virus.
        \n"Though Wyoming has not reached the dire situations of some states, this declaration will help us to prepare and mobilize resources when we need them," Gov. Mark Gordon said in a statement after requesting the declaration.
Additionally, the U.S. Virgin Islands, the Northern Mariana Islands, the District of Columbia, Guam and Puerto Rico are under disaster declarations.
Meanwhile, New Jersey moved to require facecoverings for customers picking up food from restaurants and bars
New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy issued the executive order, which will go into effect Monday at 8 p.m. Residents are already required to wear masks in grocery stores.
"Some may view this as another inconvenience," Murphy said Saturday. "But you know what would be really inconvenient is if you ended up in hospital with COVID-19 or if you infected a family member. We accept this is inconvenient."
Murphy also reported that the state has more than 58,000 cases of the virus and nearly 2,200 fatalities. The only state with more cases and deaths is New York.
He added, however, that the "curve is flattening" and the rate of new cases is slowing.
As the need for protective equipment grows, the Pentagon is moving forward with its first project under the Defense Production Act.
"The $133 million project will use these authorities to increase domestic production capacity of N95 masks to over 39 million in the next 90 days," the Pentagon said in a statement that did not include the names of the companies.
    </string>
</resources>
